

# Dilara Ozdemir

## **COMPUTER ENGINEER**

## ABOUT ME

I received a bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering from Karabuk University. Since November 2020, I have been working as an Artificial Intelligence Developer at SimurgAI, located in the Technology Development Office of Karabuk University. I have been working as a research intern at TUBITAK STAR in the Artificial Intelligence Project that we continue to develop within our company since February 2021.

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Coding Languages

Python, Matlab, C, Java, PHP, C#

Frameworks/Systems

#### **Deep Learning**

- TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

#### **Data Science**

- NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Scikit-Learn **Others**
- Ruby on Rails, Laravel

# COURSES

Neural Networks and Deep Learning/Coursera Al for Everyone/Coursera

Machine Learning Crash Course/Google Developers Signal and Image Processing, Deep Learning/TED University

Database Design and Programming with SQL/ORACLE Machine Learning, Deep Learning/IEEE TURKEY SECTION

Radar Systems Fundamentals/ASELSAN

#### DATAI TEAM

- Statistics & Python: Basic Statistics Science from
- Deep Learning and Python: Deep Learning
- Machine Learning and Python
- Data Visualization
- Data Science and Python: Expertise

# CONTACT

#### Email:

dilara.zdemir19980@gmail.com

#### Phone:

+90 553 961 21 07

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilaraozdemir/

#### Github:

https://github.com/dilaraozdemir

#### REFERENCES

Assist. Prof. Caner OZCAN

CEO, Founder of SimurgAl **Phone:** (370) 418 7050

Mail: canerozcan@karabuk.edu.tr

# EXPERIENCE

#### AI DEVELOPER

SimurgAI | Nov. 2020 -

- Object Detection, Segmentation and Analysis on MR Images via Transfer Learning

#### RESEARCH INTERN

TUBITAK | Feb. 2021 -

 Artificial Intelligence Based Automatic Analysis of Images Obtained in Dentistry (DENTIASSIST)

#### SUMMER INTERN

Karabuk University | Jun. 2020 - Aug. 2020

- Data Science, Data Analysis
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

## LABORATORY ASSISTANT

Karabuk University | Sep. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Student Assistant of CME112-Programming Languages Course

# **EDUCATION**

# KARABUK UNIVERSITY (GPA 3.24 / 4.00)

Computer Engineering Department | 2016 - 2021

- 100% English Computer Engineering Department.

#### ANADOLU UNIVERSITY

Justice Department | 2019 -

- 2nd grade student.

## PROJECTS

# ANALYSIS OF PANORAMIC DENTAL IMAGES USING ARTIFICIAL LEARNING TECHNIQUES

SimurgAI | Oct. 2020 -

As the workload of dentists is too high, treatments cannot be followed regularly, and because of the COVID-19 epidemic and similar epidemic risks in the future, less doctorpatient contact is required, as a solution, artificial intelligence supported dental radiography analysis is performed.

# SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTRA ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK R-CNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

SimurgAI | Oct. 2020 -

In the treatment and diagnosis process of teeth that need to be examined in detail in the field of dental health, bitewing intraoral radiography images are used. It is an ideal diagnostic method for the detection of recurrent caries that cannot be directly seen in the mouth, especially at the interface of small and large molars and under restorations.

# CLASSIFICATION OF HAND WRIST X-RAY IMAGES

Medathon | Apr. 2021

VGG-16, DenseNet and MobileNet networks were operated with 1000 Hand Wrist X-ray images submitted under the competition. Transfer Learning methods were used.